https://www.wgca.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The only information WGCA obtains about individual visitors to its website is information supplied voluntarily by visitors.
In cases when WGCA may need personal information to provide visitors with services tailored especially for them, or to inform them about new features or services, visitors are asked explicitly for that information.
All identifiable information provided by members (name, email or home address) will not be disclosed to anyone outside of the WGCA family.
WGCA employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions; personal information is stored in a secured database and always sent via an encrypted channel. Users may unsubscribe to any of our electronic email at any time by following the instructions contained within the email.
WGCA maintains a strict “no-spam” policy. Your information, including your email address will not be sold to any third party. If you sign up for email, you will receive only the email you have requested.
Occasionally, WGCA conducts user surveys to better target the music WGCA plays to our audience. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party.
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by WGCA only as specified above. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of all changes in our privacy policy.
If you ever feel that this site is not following the privacy policy we have described here, please contact WGCA at themix@wgca.org. We will make every reasonable effort to find and correct the problem promptly.
© 2020 WGCA
